Guide to the Volleyball records, 1973-ongoing. UA.13.02.0015
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Volleyball records
1973-ongoing.
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Sports Information Office
UA.13.02.0015
4.9 Linear Feet
5250 Items
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Volleyball records were received by the University Archives as a transfer over time.
Historical Note
The Sports Information Office provides information about Duke athletics to the media. They also facilitate press interviews with Duke athletes and coaches. For many years, the SI Office has maintained records, photographs and other material about Duke athletic teams.
Collection Overview
The collection includes clippings, press releases, statistics, rosters, programs and press brochures/media guides about the volleyball team at Duke University. The material ranges in date from 1973-ongoing.
Related Material
Athletic Dept. Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Scrapbooks.
University Archives, Duke University.
Photograph Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Photographic Negative Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Chanticleer Photograph Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Athletic Council Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Athletics Reference Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Duke University -- Volleyball -- History -- 20th century; Clippings (information artifacts); Duke University. Sports Information Office; Duke University. Sports Information Office; Duke University -- Sports
- Yearly Files, 1973-1999, 6 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  The Yearly files contain clippings, press releases, statistics, rosters, and programs about the volleyball team at Duke University.
  - 1973-1985 (Box 1)
  - 186-1990 (Box 2)
  - 1991-1993 (Box 3)
  - 1994-1995 (Box 4)
  - 1996-1997 (Box 5)
  - 1998-1999 (Box 6)
- Media Guides, 1978-ongoing, 1 boxes
  - 1978-2007 (Box 7)
  - various dates c.2 (Box 7)